#
#   This file is used to specify a name, username, email, etc... that you would
#   like to appear in the validation certificates that y-cruncher will create.
#   This is used for identification purposes.
#
#   Examples:
#               Johnny Sun   (Serotoninn)
#               Haruhi Suzumiya   (涼宮ハルヒ)
#
#
#   Note the following rules:
#       1.  It must be fewer than 1000 characters.
#       2.  Only printable characters are allowed. (i.e. No control characters)
#       3.  This file must be saved in Unicode format. (Not ASCII!!!)
#       4.  International characters are allowed as long as they are in Unicode.
#


Username:   None Specified - You can edit this in "Username.txt".
